LOUIS DE OLIVEIRA

+33 6 03 43 05 10 ♣ Bordeaux, FR ♣ DOB: 19/01/2000 ♣ French Citizenship

louisdeoliveira@gmail.com ❖ linkedin.com/in/louis-de-oliveira ❖ github.com/LouisDeOliveira

PROFILE

I am looking for a PhD student position in the field of Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning. I am experienced in the domain of Computer Vision and Computer Graphics and have been working with PyTorch for more than 3 years. I also have experience working in research and working on scientific papers thanks to my time as a research engineer at Ubisoft.

SKILLS	LANGUAGES
Python Advanced PyTorch Advanced Java/C# Intermediate TensorFlow Intermediate c/c++ Intermediate OpenCV Advanced CUDA Basics ROS Intermediate	French Native English C2 - IELTS: 8.5/9 Spanish B1
EDUCATION	
CentraleSupélec MSc - Computer Science and Engineering	
CentraleSupélec is one of France's top engineering schools, part of Univ Courses followed: Machine Learning, High Performance Computing, Soft gramming, Optimization, Signal Processing, Learning on Graphs	
KTH Royal Institute of Technology	Aug 2022 - Jan 2024 Stockholm
KTH is Sweden's top engineering university, I was enrolled in a Double-Learning master at KTH. <u>Courses followed</u> : Reinforcement Learning, Computer Vision, Robotics,	
EXPERIENCE	
Research & Development Engineer	July 2023 - Apr 2024 Bordeaux
Ubisoft's R&D center in Bordeaux, researching Real-Time 3D Neural ture that enables continuous appearance of materials across scales (see Splatting methods for real-time appearance modelling. <u>Technologies used</u> : Pytorch, c++, HLSL, Hydra, Unreal Engine	
Software Engineering Consultant	May 2022 - Oct 2022 Paris

Design and implementation of a **Python** delivery-scheduling software using meta-heuristics and parallel-computing in order to generate schedules efficiently for a swimming pool shell manufacturer. Technologies used: Ray, Numpy

PUBLICATIONS

[1] Louis de Oliveira, Clément Weinreich, Antoine Houdard, and Georges Nader. Real-Time Neural Materials using Block-Compressed Features, October 2023. https://arxiv.org/abs/2311.16121, Computer Graphics Forum 2024.

PROJECTS

I also work on multiple projects on my spare time that can be accessed on my GitHub. These projects include Robotics, Reinforcement Learning, Deep Learning and GPU programming work.